let questions5 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "aware",
        answer: "B. sich bewusst",
        options: [
            "A. sich erinnern",
            "B. sich bewusst",
            "C. sich entschuldigen",
            "D. sich beschweren"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "badly",
        answer: "A. schlecht",
        options: [
            "A. schlecht",
            "B. unangenehm",
            "C. unglücklich",
            "D. ungünstig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "to belong",
        answer: "C. gehören",
        options: [
            "A. gehorchen",
            "B. gelten",
            "C. gehören",
            "D. gelingen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to continue",
        answer: "A. fortsetzen",
        options: [
            "A. fortsetzen",
            "B. erweitern",
            "C. verlängern",
            "D. wiederholen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "error",
        answer: "D. Fehler",
        options: [
            "A. Illusion",
            "B. Unglück",
            "C. Missverständnis",
            "D. Fehler"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "experience",
        answer: "B. Erfahrung",
        options: [
            "A. Begegnung",
            "B. Erfahrung",
            "C. Kenntnis",
            "D. Abenteuer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "field",
        answer: "C. Feld",
        options: [
            "A. Platz",
            "B. Gebiet",
            "C. Feld",
            "D. Wiese"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to hurt",
        answer: "A. verletzen",
        options: [
            "A. verletzen",
            "B. zerstören",
            "C. ruinieren",
            "D. schrecken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "judgment",
        answer: "D. Urteil",
        options: [
            "A. Anklage",
            "B. Gericht",
            "C. Strafe",
            "D. Urteil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "likely",
        answer: "B. wahrscheinlich",
        options: [
            "A. erlaubt",
            "B. wahrscheinlich",
            "C. sicherlich",
            "D. ungewiss"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "normal",
        answer: "C. normal",
        options: [
            "A. natürlich",
            "B. gewöhnlich",
            "C. normal",
            "D. standard"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "rare",
        answer: "A. selten",
        options: [
            "A. selten",
            "B. außergewöhnlich",
            "C. unerwartet",
            "D. sporadisch"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to relax",
        answer: "B. entspannen",
        options: [
            "A. beruhigen",
            "B. entspannen",
            "C. loslassen",
            "D. nachlassen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to request",
        answer: "C. anfordern",
        options: [
            "A. freuen",
            "B. fordern",
            "C. anfordern",
            "D. suchen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to reside",
        answer: "B. wohnen",
        options: [
            "A. bleiben",
            "B. wohnen",
            "C. verweilen",
            "D. übernachten"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "result",
        answer: "D. Ergebnis",
        options: [
            "A. Ausgang",
            "B. Folge",
            "C. Konsequenz",
            "D. Ergebnis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to roll",
        answer: "A. rollen",
        options: [
            "A. rollen",
            "B. kippen",
            "C. wenden",
            "D. schleudern"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "since",
        answer: "B. seit",
        options: [
            "A. bevor",
            "B. seit",
            "C. während",
            "D. weil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "visible",
        answer: "C. sichtbar",
        options: [
            "A. erkennbar",
            "B. deutlich",
            "C. sichtbar",
            "D. wahrnehmbar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "wild",
        answer: "A. wild",
        options: [
            "A. wild",
            "B. böse",
            "C. gefährlich",
            "D. unkontrolliert"
        ]
    }
];
